字幕制作：太子
It's all for the wish of birthday to LiJie
片名：鬼娃回魂3
这是这是安迪・巴克利
This is Andy Barclay.
八年前，他引发的一起事件
Eight years ago,he touched off the scandal
差点使公司倒闭
that nearly crippled this company,
声称他的好家伙玩偶，恰吉
claiming that his Good Guy doll, Chucky,
被查尔斯・李・雷附身
was possessed by Charles Lee Ray,
一个声名狼藉的湖畔杀人犯
the notorious Lakeshore Strangler.
征求意见，女士们和先生们
Now I ask you,ladies and gentlemen,
在所有的诉讼和负面言论之后
after all the lawsuits and negative publicity,
公司最终决定恢复生产这个“好家伙”
when the company is finally getting back on its feet again,
讨论一下此产品推回到市场有何明智之举？
where is the wisdom in putting the Good Guy back on the market?
沙利文先生，在事件发生之前
Mr. Sullivan,before any of this happened,
“好家伙”娃娃的销量是其他娃娃的两倍
the Good Guy outsold all our other toys 2-to-I.
即使现在，市场的需求兴趣点也是在最巅峰
Even now, interest in the market place is at its peak.
工厂已经进入再次量产阶段
The factory is up and running again.
在下周之前产品应进入各大商店
We should be in stores by next week.
我们不能让一个有“恐慌症”的孩子
We cannot let the fantasies of one disturbed boy
来影响了公司的效益
influence company policy.
还有，如果这种娃娃以消极的方式
Well, what if the doll somehow affects
影响了其他的孩子
another child in a negative way?
在你心里可能就会有一种无法摆脱的公共梦魇
You could have a public relations nightmare on your hands.
你们知道，这笔生意最难过的坎
You know, one of the hardest things about this business
就是这是一笔生意
is that it is a business.
我们卖什么并不重要
It doesn’t matter what we’re selling.
无论是汽车，核武器，甚至是玩具
Whether it’s cars,nuclear weapons, or, yes, even toys.
问题的关键在于
The bottom line is the bottom line.
孩子们算什么，毕竟，还是新生消费者
And what are children,after all,but consumer trainees
安迪・巴克利已经成为历史
Andy Barclay is ancient history.
没人记得他，没人关注他
No one remembers him. Nobody cares.
我已经决定
I have made up my mind.
要继续向前发展
We’re moving ahead.
谢谢大家
Thank you.
- 好的 - 好的
- Okay - All right.
沙利文先生
Mr. Sullivan.
若没之前的事，我会全力支持你
If there’s nothing I can say to convince you,
但是我现在必须要表明我的立场
then I must go on record with my position.
我非常反对这样做
I’m completely against this.
你的立场已经很清楚了，迈尔斯
Your position is crystal clear, Miles,
你也知道我也不会忘记历史的
and you can be sure I won’t forget.
朋友们，稍等一下
Just a minute, folks! Please.
沙利文先生，有个小惊喜
Mr. Sullivan, we have a little surprise for you.
工厂那边送来的
The guys at the factory sent this over.
我们都希望你会收下它
And we all wanted you to have it.
这是第一个下线的产品
It’s the first one off the assembly line.
90年代的“好家伙”
The Good Guy of the ‘90s!
好吧，如果没事了，我要撤了
Well, if there’s nothing  else,I’m gonna get going.
走吧
Fine.
就是，我老婆在等我呢
It’s just,my wife’s expecting me.
今天是结婚周年日
It’s our anniversary.
走吧，佩佐德
Fine, Petzold.
我想，晚餐之后重新仔细研究下市场调研报告
Well, I guess I could review the Larrabee report after dinner.
晚安，沙利文先生
Good night,Mr. Sullivan.
晚安
Good night.
尽管股市趋势疲软
Well, despite a downdraft in the bond market,
各大股东依然会迅速重整旗鼓
stocks were able to post a rally on Friday,
这里要感谢各大工厂的鼎力相助
thanks to a couple of different factors.
强于预期的就业报告
Not only did the stronger-than-expected employment report
不仅减轻了经济的衰退
allay some recession fears,
而且使部分个股出现技术性反弹
but also there was a technical rebound in stock,
空头回补，持续买进
short covering, program buying,
并且帮助了在个股交易中
and the resurgence in the deal stocks
资金的回转和定下私募起点
help set the tone for rally on the Street.
下面我们看一下数据
Here’s a look at the numbers now.
本周五，道琼斯指数提升了16个百分点占比三分之二
For Friday, the Dow Industrial’s up sixteen and two-thirds.
今日涨幅最高点中
Of the highs of the day,
其交易量稍好一点，要比同期提升三倍
the transportation average up a little better than three.
公共事业股涨幅均为 12点，22点，61点，78点
Utilities bouncing up a point to pass at 12, at22, 61, 78.
S&P 500指数显示交易峰值多达两个
S&P 500 Cash are better than two
（S&P500指标准普尔500指数，仅次于道琼斯的一种反应股票市场的数据分析方法，可以去问下度娘）
同比增高了接近2.5倍
with the margin peaking up almost two and a half
最后以1.59的涨幅率收官
with the premier ending at 1.59.
纽约证券交易所涨幅率达到1.23
New York Stock Exchange Index up 1.23,
收仓成交量达到1.64亿股
volume backing off a bit at 164 million shares.
白天纽约证券交易所
Advances beat declines just about
成交量继续持续走高
9-to-5 on the New York Stock Exchange.
涨幅成交量达到1.03亿股，跌幅成交量......
The up volume 103 million shares,the down volume...
（本人不炒股，以上各术语要是有错译，漏译，敬请各位看官海涵，毕竟和剧情几乎无关）
仅仅就在那小段时间里.....
In just a moment’s time...
哪去了？
Where is it?
啊
Ah.
嘿，我叫拉瑞
Hi, my name is Larry.
嘿，我叫泼瑞
Hi, my name is Pauly.
- 嘿，想玩玩么？- 嘿，想玩玩么？
- Hey, wanna play? - Hey, wanna play?
- 我喜欢被拥抱 - 我喜欢被拥抱
- I like to be hugged. - I like to be hugged.
嘿，我叫拉瑞
Hi, my name is Larry.
嘿，我叫泼瑞
Hi, my name is Pauly.
- 嘿，想玩玩么？- 嘿，想玩玩么？
- Hey, wanna play? - Hey, wanna play?
- 我喜欢被拥抱 - 我喜欢被拥抱
- I like to be hugged. - I like to be hugged.
嘿，我叫拉瑞
Hi, my name is Larry.
嘿，我叫泼瑞
Hi, my name is Pauly.
- 嘿，想玩玩么？- 嘿，想玩玩么？
- Hey, wanna play? - Hey, wanna play?
- 我喜欢被.....
- I like to be...
别他妈的惹恰吉！
Don’t fuck with the Chuck!
哦，天啊
Oh, my God.
正中靶心！
Bull’s-eye!
就像当年的欢乐时光！
Just like the good old days！
勒死是最流行的最直接的
Nothing like a strangulation to get the circulation going.
你是让我移魂出窍的仅存票根，安迪！
You’re my only ticket out of here, Andy.
我就想从这个该死娃娃壳里出去
I got to get out of this goddamn body.
你在哪呢，小混蛋？
Where are you, you little shit?
档案：安迪・巴克利
年龄：16周岁
被肯特军校缓释入取
.....................
肯特军校
[KENT MILITARY SCHOOL]
向左向右，转！
Inward, hut!
加油，加油，你一定行的
Come on.Come on, yeah!You can do it!
加油，你行的，杰克逊，加油
Come on. You can do it,Jackson, hurry up.
不错，继续，很好！
Yeah! Move. Yes!
加油，继续向前，赶快
Come on. Let’s go.Yeah! Come on.
继续前进，向终点进发！
Get moving! Go to the end of the line!
我看到在过去的八年里
I see that for the past eight years
你被寄养在他人家庭中
you’ve been in one foster home after another.
介意我知道原因么？
Mind if I ask why?
他们把我从妈妈身边带走
They took me away from my mother.
她是......迫不得已而为之
She’s ....under special care.
我知道
I know that.
我是说你怎么就不能安定在某个地方呢？
I meant how come you never got settled anywhere?
男孩指认杀手附身“玩偶娃娃”
换换环境
Adjustment problems.
我认字，巴克利
I can read, Barclay.
我要你口头回答
I’m asking you.
和那些人在一起就从没舒服过
I never felt comfortable with those people.
他们不是我的家人，是陌生人
They weren’t family, they were strangers.
好吧，听着，巴克利
All right, listen up, Barclay.
我很乐意修理修理你，因为你太不老实了
I’m willing to cut you some sack because you’ve had it so rough,
总是到处惹麻烦
but you’re a troublemaker.
现在我正式接手了你这个小捣蛋鬼
And I got a real problem with troublemakers.
在军校捣乱可是不行的
They don’t fit into the system.
给你几条忠告
So here’s my advice.
长大点吧，你再也不是个孩子了
Grow up, you’re not a kid anymore.
是时候忘记那些杀手玩偶的幻想了
It’s time to forget these fantasies of killer dolls.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
“当我还是个孩子的时候，我像孩子一样的思考”
“When I was a child,I thought as a child.
“但是当我成为男人时，我就远离了儿时的天真”
“But when I became a man,I put away childish things.”
小新兵
First Corinthians.
注意口令，巴克利，起立！
Look alive,Barclay, on your feet!
在肯特军校，我们接收尿床的蠢蛋，然后把他们变成男人
At Kent, we take bedwetters and turn them into men.
哦，不错，不错！
Oh, yes. Yes.
真不错！
Oh, yes!
我们都能看到头皮了，是吧？
We’re seeing some skin now, aren’t we?
滚吧！剪成光头了
Presto! You’re bald.
一开始总会感觉有点怪异
Always feels a little weird at first.
下一位
Next.
和它吻别吧
Kiss it goodbye.
知道吧，罗马人发明的大兵头
You know, the Romans invented the military cut.
知道为什么吗？
You know why?
为什么？
Why?
把头发剪短了
To keep their hair short
那在战争中敌人就无法抓头
so their enemies couldn’t grab ahold of it in battle
然后也无法割喉
and slit their throat.
现在，坐稳了
Now, hold still.
哦，该死
Oh, shit.
我们又回来了，我们比以往更卡哇伊了
We’re back,and we’re better than ever.
没人愿意和我玩
No one will play with me.
哦-哦，有一位孤单的小伙伴
Uh-oh.There’s a friend in need.
嘿，振作点
Hey, cheer up!
你是谁？
Who are you?
我是好家伙
I’m a Good Guy.
好家伙，好家伙，好家伙，好家伙！
Good Guy! Good Guy! Good Guy! Good Guy!
我刚刚从好家伙之家赶来
I’ve just come from the Good Guy Clubhouse,
我将永远成为你的小伙伴
and I’ll be your friend till the end.
做我小伙伴？
You will?
哇哦！
Wow!
当然
Sure I will.
嘿-N-吼
Hidey-h o!
来吧，和我一起尽享高飞的乐趣吧，永远做你的小伙伴
So, all aboard for high-flying fun with me,your friend till the end,
我是来自“玩偶伙伴”的“好家伙”
the Good Guy doll from Play Pals.
得了吧，哥们
Come on, man!
你还好吧？
Are you okay?
杂碎们，狗杂碎们！
The bastards! Fucking bastards!
咋回事？
What happened?
谢尔顿，就是那帮狗杂碎
Shelton,that’s what happened.
谢尔顿和他的潘啃∴们
Shelton and his goddamn lackeys.
谢了，我没事
Thank you. I’m fine.
我叫安迪
I’m Andy.
你一定是新来的
You must be new.
不然你不会不知道这里的规矩
Otherwise you’d know they don’t tolerate any form of individuality here.
名字中“名”全部都是公开的
Certainly nothing so personal as the first name.
啊，对，我忘了，我姓巴克利
Yeah, right, I forgot.Barclay.
怀特・赫斯特，档案上是哈洛德・奥布瑞
Whitehurst.Harold Aubrey for the record.
那，谢尔顿是谁？
So, who’s this Shelton?
军校助理，布雷特・C・谢尔顿上校
Cadet Lieutenant Colonel Brett C. Shelton.
这里他就是上帝
He’s God around here.
不要幻想他会仁慈
Don’t expect any mercy from him.
欢迎来到地狱，巴克利
Welcome to hell, Barclay.
全体集合完毕，长官
All present and accounted for, sir.
稍息，埃尔斯少校
Thank you, Major Ellis.
你新来的，是吧？
You’re the new boy, huh?
是
Yeah.
感觉咋样？
How you doing?
- 非常好 - 那就好
- Pretty good. - Good.
谁说了你可以向我直视的？
Who said you could look at me?
知道我是谁么？
Do you know who I am?
谢尔顿？
Shelton?
对你来说是军校助理谢尔顿上校，混蛋！
That’s Lieutenant Colonel Shelton to you, asshole!
军校助理谢尔顿上校
Lieutenant Colonel Shelton.
不对，是“军校助理谢尔顿上校”
No. Lieutenant Colonel Shelton,
“长官”
sir.
军校助理谢尔顿上校，长官
Lieutenant Colonel Shelton, sir.
叫啥名，傻瓜？
What’s your name,dipweed?
巴克利
Barclay.
- 长官 - 大声点
- Sir. - Louder.
- 长官 - 再大声点
- Sir! - Louder!
- 长官
- Sir!
这才像点样，新来的，这才像点样
That’s much better, new boy.That’s much better.
妈的，怀特・赫斯特
Shit, Whitehurst.
你们不用怀疑
You are without a doubt
这是我见过最悲哀的事
the most pathetic thing I have ever seen!
你们同意不？
Wouldn’t you agree?
我问你话呢，小子
I asked you a nimrod! question,
不，长官，我不同意，长官
No, sir! I don’t agree, sir!
你在反驳我吧，认为我是在胡扯吗？
Are you contradicting me,you sorry-ass sack of shit?
去你妈的
You asshole.
你刚说什么？
What did you say?
我刚说“去你妈的”，长官！
I said,“You asshole,” sir!
你以为你挺搞笑的，是吧，德・斯尔娃？
You think you’re pretty funny,don’t you, De Silva?
是，挺搞笑，长官
Yes, I do, sir.
那你现在何不赶紧趴下做25个？
Why don’t you drop and give me 25 right now?
25个啥，长官？
Twenty-five what, sir?
25个俯卧撑，德・斯尔娃
Twenty-five push-ups,De Silva.
一个，长官，两个，长官...
One, sir. Two, sir...
现在，你们女生可能以为....
Now, you women might think that
你们比其他人更加脆弱
because you’re so much more delicate,
你们就该受到一些优待
you deserve some sort of special treatment,
但是我们只有一个月，你们必须抛弃那些鬼想法
and once a month we’re just going to get on out of your way.
十二个，长官，十三个，长官
Twelve, sir.Thirteen, sir.
就是，忘掉那些恶习
Well, you can forget it.
每人都要遵守同一篇规章制度
The same rules apply for everybody.
十八个，长官，十九个，长官
Eighteen, sir. Nineteen, sir.
适者生存
Only the fittest survive.
廿二个，长官，廿三个，长官
Twenty-two, sir.Twenty-three, sir.
一只手
One-handed.
廿四个，长官
Twenty-four, sir.
廿五个，长官
Twenty-five, sir.
归队
Recover.
今天过的咋样，泰勒？
How you doing, Tyler?
抱歉，今天没你爸爸的信，明天来吧
Sorry. Nothing from your dad today.Maybe tomorrow.
听着，他忙着开战斗机，保卫国家
Listen,he’s busy flying jets,defending the country.
他一有机会就会写信给你的
He’ll write to you when he gets the chance.
我知道
I know.
嘿
Hey!
帮我做件事
I got a job for you.
能把这个给那个新来的吗？巴克利
Would you give this to the new kid for me? Barclay.
好的，长官
Yes, sir.
好孩子
Attaboy.
哇喔
Whoa.
看着点，小子！算了，你怎么能这么笨？
Watch it, kid! Anyway, how could you be so stupid?
嘿，看着点
Hey, look out!
军械库
好家伙娃娃
A Good Guy.
你他妈的是谁？
Who the fuck are you?
我以为你们只会说三句话呢
I thought you guys only said three sentences.
我是最新改良升级版的
I’m new and improved.
我以前从没看过像你这样的娃娃
I never saw a doll like you before.
好吧，孩子，不开玩笑了
All right, kid,fun’s over.
他妈的安迪在哪？
Where the hell’s Andy?
安迪？
Andy?
你不认字么？
Can’t you read?
这件包裹是寄给他的
He was supposed to get this package.
偷拆邮件可是大罪哦
Tampering with the mail is a federal offense.
抱歉，他是你的好基友么？
Sorry.Is he your best friend?
比那还亲，他简直是我生命中的曙光
He’s more than that.He’s my new lease on life.
等等
Wait a minute.
这有现成的新身体
I got a new body,
和他移魂之后不说出我的秘密就行了
and I ain’t told anyone about my little secret yet.
你叫啥名，孩子？
So, what’s your name, kid?
泰勒，你的呢？
Tyler. What’s yours?
恰吉，但是
Chucky. But, uh,
我的真名叫查尔斯・李・雷
my real name is Charles Lee Ray.
(GUNS FIRING)
怀特・赫斯特，我总是打偏！
Whitehurst,what am I doing wrong?
还有什么你办不到的么？
Is there anything you can’t do?
有啊，看起来我离不开这里了
Yeah. I can’t seem to get thrown out of this place.
巴克利，见过德・斯尔娃了
Barclay,meet De Silva.
嘿
Hi.
嗯，能指导指导我么？
So, want to show me?
- 当然，可以！ - 谢谢！
- Yeah, sure. - Okay.
不，肘部放低....对，就这样
No. Put the elbow...Yeah, like that.
然后这样
And like this.
不，两只眼睛都睁开
No. Keep both eyes open.
视线要盯住目标
Keep your sights on the target.
稳住呼吸
Now hold your breath.
扣紧扳机，不要太紧了
Squeeze the trigger,don’t pull it.
你很不专心
You’re not concentrating.
知道吗，在集合时你为我们所做的，真的是棒极了
You know, it was really great what you did for us back there at formation.
是的，谢尔顿就是个二逼
Well,Shelton’s a major dick.
给我讲讲他的事
Tell me about it.
我们就玩捉迷藏行么？
Couldn’t we just play hide-and-seek?
淡定哦
Hold still.
随便了，你怎么叫这个游戏？
What do you call this game anyway?
“灵魂隐匿”  相信我，你会喜欢的
Hide the Soul. Trust me.You’re gonna love it.
随你怎么说吧，查尔斯
Whatever you say,Charles.
（喃嘛呢叭咪耍喃嘛呢叭咪耍
我祈求你，赐予我力量吧！
Give me the power,I beg of you!
（喃嘛呢叭咪耍喃嘛呢叭咪耍
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
我们将队伍整体分成两队
So we divide the troops in half,
- 每一队大约是70人 - 妈的
- thaVll be about 70 on each team. - Shit!
查尔斯，停止宣誓
Charles, stop swearing.
每位队员，我们都需要
Per soldier,and we’re gonna need
配备一支装填0-3爆花弹的...是的，长官
the Springfield O-3s...Yes, sir.
然后将两队分别标记为红队和蓝队
marked for both the red team and the blue team.
你干嘛呢，泰勒？
What are you doing,Tyler?
我们在玩“灵魂隐匿”
We’re playing Hide the Soul.
我等会去找你
I’ll catch up with you.
我先去装颜料
I’ll start loading the paint pellet.
不要玩娃娃，好不，泰勒？
We don’t play with dolls,do we  now, Tyler?
女孩才玩娃娃的
Dolls are for girls.
但是查尔斯是我的新基友
But Charles is my new best friend.
泰勒，不要和高级长官顶嘴
Tyler, you know better than to talk back to a superior officer.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
把这弄干净
Clean that up.
娃娃交给我
I’ll take care of this.
我会回来的！
I’ll be back!
一！一！一，二，一！
Left! Left! Left, right, left!
一！一！
Left! Left!
枪拿高点，巴克利
Get that weapon up,Barclay!
立，定！
Platoon, halt!
向左转！
Left face!
新兵，出列！
New boy, fall out!
出列！
Fall out!
预备，操枪！
Order, hut!
胸前，上！
Port, arms!
右肩，上！
Right shoulder, arms!
左肩，上！
Left shoulder, arms!
右肩，上！
Right shoulder, arms!
左肩，上！
Left shoulder, arms!
胸前，上！
Port, arms!
左肩，上！
Left shoulder, arms!
胸前，上！
Port, arms!
右肩，上！
Right shoulder, arms!
(GARBLED COMMANDS)
巴克利！
Barclay!
这可不是棍子，巴克利
It’s not a baton,Barclay.
你他妈的看起来就像个乐队指挥
You look like a goddamn majorette over here.
我还不习惯用枪，长官
I’m not used to guns, sir.
在你看来这像是一把枪么，巴克利？
Does this look like a gun to you, Barclay?
这是把步枪
It’s a rifle!
- 埃尔斯少校？- 长官
- Major Ellis? - Sir!
给新兵蛋子看看枪和步枪的区别
Would you please show the new boy the difference?
这是我的步枪，这是我的枪
This is my rifle,this is my gun.
这个是用来射杀的，这个是娱乐的
This is for shooting,and this is for fun.
枪是士兵的最好的基友
A soldier’s rifle is his best friend.
记住
Remember that.
停
Stop!
妈的
Shit!
救命！求你了，先生！
Help!Please, mister!
救命啊，来人啊
Please, somebody!
天啊
Jesus!
我被卡住了，先生
I’m stuck，Mister!
我在车斗里
I’m in here!
坚持住，我来了
Hold on. I’m coming!
你在哪了？
Where are you?
我来了
I’m coming.
叫喊一下！弄点声音
Yell or something!Make a noise!
你在哪？
Where are you?
你他妈....
What the...
哦，天啊
Oh, my God.
不！停下！
No! Stop!
停下
Stop!
解散
Fall out.
去后面看看
You get back there.
最好把包裹打包好，巴克利
Better finish unpacking,Barclay.
谢尔顿的突然“紧急集合”是出名的
Shelton’s notorious for surprise inspections.
你在干嘛了？
What are you doing?
我像在干嘛？在给谢尔顿的鞋子上光
What does it look like? I’m polishing Shelton’s shoes.
他让你给鞋子上光？
He makes you polish his shoes?
不，我是良心发现，发发善心
No, I offered out of the kindness of my heart.
怀特・赫斯特，你看到科克伦今天和那个娃娃了吗？
Whitehurst,did you see Cochrane
with that doll today?
没，什么娃娃？
No. What doll?
他拿着一个好家伙娃娃
He was carrying a Good Guy doll,
就在垃圾车出事之前
just before the accident with the garbage truck.
好家伙，我想起来了
Good Guys,I remember those.
是的，我也是
Yeah, me, too.
呃，马上熄灯了
Uh, lights out in a few inutes.
我要去洗漱一下
I’m going to go get washed up.
巴克利，我差点忘了
Barclay,I almost forgot.
克拉克军士想知道你收到了包裹没
Sergeant Clark wanted to know if you got that package.
什么包裹？
What package?
他说那个泰勒小孩
He said you got a package in the mail.
应该给你一个被邮寄过来的包裹
That little kid Tyler was supposed to bring it to you.
- 难道你没收到？- 没收到
- Didn’t you get it? - No.
谁会给我邮寄包裹呢？
Who would’ve sent me a package?
嘿，好久不见，哥们
Hey,long time no see, pal.
不，你早死了，我们杀死你了
No, you’re dead. We killed you!
你知道他们说的
You know what they say,
你不会让好家伙停产滞销的
you just can’t keep a Good Guy down.
安迪，你都长大了
Andy, how you’ve grown.
你不能杀我的，你需要我
You’re not gonna kill me. You need me.
你需要向我的身体里移魂
You need to transfer your soul into my body.
又错了，胆小鬼
Wrong again, wimp.
计划中我有新选择了
I got some fresh meat lined up
我不会让你毁掉计划的，这次不行
and I’m not gonna let you spoil it, not this time.
泰勒
Tyler.
是，想想吧，恰吉将会是好基友
Yeah, just think. Chucky’s gonna be a bro.
我不会让你成功的
I’m not gonna let you get away with this.
我不会让你靠近那孩子的
I’m not gonna let you near that kid.
怎么了，巴克利，想家了？
What’s the matter,Barclay, huh? You homesick?
想你老妈了？
You miss your mommy?
这他妈怎么个事？
What the fuck is this?
真对不起，我错了，我会擦亮的
I’m sorry about your shoe, all right. I’ll polish it.
就是，求你把娃娃还我
Just give me back the doll.
不，不行，给我听着
No, no, you listen to me.
你告诉怀特・赫斯特他解脱了，懂没？
You tell Whitehurst he’s off the hook, huh?
我会另找苦工的
I got myself another slave.
把这一堆收拾干净，你会被记五次大过的
And clean up this mess.You got five demerits.
那娃娃呢？
What about the doll?
哦，我妹的生日要到了
Ah. My kid sister’s birthday is coming up.
我想她会喜欢的，你说呢？
I think she’s gonna love it,don’t you?
哦，妈的
Oh, shit.
安迪
Andy.
怎么个率拢
What the fuck?
不要，停下
No, stop!
你在我房间干他妈啥呢，巴克利？
What the fuck are you doing in my room, Barclay?
你不会相信我的
You wouldn’t believe me.
娃娃呢，巴克利？
Where’s the doll, Barclay?
他妈的娃娃哪去了？
Where’s the fucking doll?
- 你偷走了，是不？ - 不是
- You took it,didn’t you? - No!
怎么回事？
What’s going on?
是的，肯定有人偷走了
Yeah, well, somebody sure as hell took it.
马上就子夜了，上校
It’s almost midnight,Colonel.
真的有这个必要么？
Is this really necessary?
我正在搜查一个小偷，长官
I’m trying to weed out a thief, sir.
你总是一再告诫我
You’ve always told me how important it is
维持学校荣誉的重要性
to uphold the school’s code of honor.
我就是要让他们吃住这个教训，长官
I’m simply trying to impress that upon the men, sir.
好吧，谢尔顿，继续坚持吧
All right, Shelton, make your point.
但是凌晨一点前必须回去
But I want everybody back inside at 0100 hours.
是，长官
Yes, sir.
在我们搞定巴克利之前
By the time we get through with Barclay,
我会让他过着生不如屎的生活
he’s going to be living in a whole world full of shit.
好吧，还剩下一小时了，开始计时吧
All right.We’ve only got an hour,so let’s make it count.
是的长官
Yes, sir.
好了，女士们，举起武器
All right, ladies,get those weapons in the air.
我想看到枪被举高了
I want to see ‘em high!
在高点
Higher!
我想我快吐了
I think I’m gonna throw up.
你死定了，新兵蛋子
You’re dead, new boy.
去你妈的
Fucking geek.
“亲爱的查尔斯，你看到留言了”
“Dear Charles, you’re it.
“来找我吧，你的好朋友，泰勒”
“Come and find me,your best friend.”
妈的
Shit.
查尔斯
Charles.
来找我吧
Come and find me!
他妈的
God damn it.
- 前进   - 进攻
- Platoon! - Hut!
在来一次
Double time!
进攻
Hut!
膝盖抬起来，女士们
Get those knees up,ladies!
怀特・赫斯特，孩子们在哪睡觉？
Whitehurst,where do the kids sleep?
在门廊上面，怎么了？
Above the portico. Why?
你们穿的是军靴，不是芭比舞鞋
You’re wearing combat boots,not ballet slippers.
- 快，快！- 巴克利？
- Come on, move! - Barclay?
战场上永远都比这残酷
It’s gonna get a lot worse than this!
用力向前，快，快！
Get the lead out. Come on, move it!
快点，快点，布鲁克，快点！
Faster, faster.Let’s go, B rock!
膝盖在抬高点，快
Get those knees in the sky! Come on!
你他妈的
You son of a bitch!
你他妈的摊上大事了，巴克利
You got a hell of a punch there, Barclay.
让我看看你骨头到底有多硬
Now I’ll see what kind of tough guy you really are.
把头抬起来
Get your head around.
泰勒，出来，出来，你在哪呢？
Tyler, come out, come out,wherever you are.
抓到你了哦！
Oily oiiy oxen free.
赶紧出来你这个小混蛋
Get out here,you little son of a bitch.
- 三 - 三
- Three! - Three!
还是不够狠
You’re not sounding off.
四
Four!
真他妈的让我恼火
You’re pissing me off!
五
Five!
我服了，巴克利，你可真让我服了
All right, Barclay,you got me curious.
你到底想要证明什么？
What are you trying to prove?
算了，别提了
Forget it.
不，真的，我想知道
No, really, I want to know.
好吧
All right.
那个娃娃是活的，它正找泰勒呢
The doll’s alive.He’s after Tyler.
你是对的，算了，忘了吧
You’re right,forget it.
祈祷泰勒能自己搞定吧
I just hope he can take care of himself.
- 这边 - 好，好的
- Come on. - Okay, okay.
小点声
Quiet.
别出声
Shut up.
好的，来吧
Okay, come on.
来啊
Come on.
真不敢相信我能带你一起来干这个
I can’t believe I let you talk me into this.
好了，呆在这帮我把风
Okay, just stay here and keep an eye out,okay?
好，我最擅长把风的
Oh, I live for this.
我知道，伊芙，好了，去吧，去吧
I know, Ivers.Now, go, go!
知道吗，我真不知道那小子有啥特别的，真的
You know, I don’t see what you see in that guy, anyway.
我也不知道，他就是....就是有点特别
I don’t know, he’s...Well, he’s just different from everybody else.
哦，拉倒吧
Oh, please.
哦，他还有一点可爱
Oh, he’s kind of cute, too.
呵呵
Mmm.
好了
Okay.
寄养家庭，难怪这么内向
Foster homes. No wonder he’s so quiet.
什么声音
What was that?
是你偷走了娃娃
So you took the doll?
谢尔顿要是知道你会上军事法庭的
Shelton will have you court-martialed if he finds out.
我们在玩捉迷藏，你们在干嘛？
We’re playing Hide and Seek.What are you guys doing?
我们睡不着
We couldn’t sleep.
啊，它太可爱了
Oh, he is so cute.
伊芙，我先找到它的，还给我，还给我
Ivers, he was mine first!Give him back! Give him back!
你们这些家伙，能安静点不？
You guys,please be quiet.
你去站岗把风
Can you go stand guard?
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
它叫啥名？
So what’s his name?
- 你自己问它 - 好吧
- Ask him yourself - All right.
你叫啥名，小娃娃？
What is your name,little doll?
嘿，我是恰吉，你一生相伴的好基友
Hi, I’m Chucky.And I’m your friend to the end.
嘿-N-吼
Hidey-ho!
爱死它了
I love it.
他的真名叫查尔斯・李・雷
His real name is Charles Lee Ray.
哦，是吗？口红给我
Oh, is that so? Give me your lipstick.
- 干嘛？ - 给我吧
- What for? - Just give it to me.
哦，给
Oh, here.
你做什么呢？
What are you doing?
瞧着吧
You’ll see.
等等，停下来
Wait. Stop.
- 怎么样，小宝贝！ - 别这样
- Here you go,little baby! - Come on!
你会把它弄脏的
You’re messing him up.
哦，你太可爱了
Oh, you’re so cute.
- 别那么做 - 啊哦
- Don’t do that! - Aw.
不要，它看起来太傻了
Don’t. He looks stupid.
你把他弄的和傻瓜一样
You’re making him look like a wuss.
天啊，看起来太美了，你干嘛呢？
No, he looks sweet.What are you doing?
注意点，有人来了
You guys, someone’s coming.
好了，赶紧撤
Come on, let’s go.
快，快撤，等等，等等
Come on. Let’s go.Wait, wait.
等会，查尔斯怎么办？
Stop! What about Charles?
这简直是宣战
This means war.
这怎么回事？
What the hell?
我喜欢被拥抱
I like to be hugged.
哦，你他妈的不是在耍我吧？
Oh, you got to be fucking kidding me!
这家伙今晚还来回巡逻了两次
A man lives through two tours in Nam
然后现在就突然挂了
and then one night he just drops dead.
没有任何征兆
Doesn’t make any sense.
跨立！
At ease!
谨此
We will now take a moment of silence
向科克伦上尉默哀
to honor Colonel Cochrane.
他生前如此和蔼，我们将终生怀念
He was a fine man and he will be sorely missed.
低头默哀
Bow your heads for prayer.
就坐
Take seats!
卡尔森，头发越来越长了
It’s getting pretty shaggy, Carison.
下周五过来
I want to see you on Friday.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
周一，卷毛小子
Monday, Fabrizzio.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
乖孩子
My man.
周二
Tuesday.
瞅瞅你，怀特・赫斯特，你真他妈的丢脸
Look at you, Whitehurst.You’re a disgrace.
上次剪头是什么时候？
When’s the last time you had a trim?
差不多两周前，长官
Two weeks ago,Sergeant, I think.
差不多？差不多？
You think? You think?
吃完早餐立刻去见我 明白不？
I want to see you right after breakfast. You got it?
是的，波尼克军士，长官
Yes, sir,Sergeant Botnick, sir.
你瞅什么呢，新兵蛋子？
And what are you looking at, new boy?
周三
Wednesday.
巴克利，你干嘛去？
Barclay,what are you doing?
你不能胡来
You can’t just get up in the middle of mess.
闭嘴
Shut up.
少校
Major.
肃静
At ease!
泰勒
Tyler.
嘿，巴克利，咋回事？
Hi, Barclay. What’s up?
我要和你谈谈恰吉
I gotta talk to you about Chucky.
你是说查尔斯
You mean Charles.
你见过他了么？
Have you seen him?
昨晚以后就没见到过
Not since last night.
他一定藏起来了
He’s hiding somewhere.
他一知道你是自己一个人
He’s gonna lay low till he knows you’re alone,
就会过来找你
and then he’s gonna come after you.
他就是想玩游戏
He just wants to play.
听我说，泰勒
Listen to me, Tyler.
无论他说什么，无论他向你承诺什么
No matter what he says,no matter what he promises you,
你都要离他远远的
you’ve got to stay away from him.
不要让他骗了你，他是坏人
Don’t let him fool you.He’s bad.
查尔斯才不坏呢，他是好家伙
Charles isn’t bad.He’s a Good Guy.
我可以替他担保
It says so on his shirt.
他撒谎，泰勒
He lies, Tyler.
相信我，他是坏人
Believe me,he’s bad news.
他已经伤害许多人了
He’s hurt a lot of people.
科克伦上尉就是被他害死得
I think Colonel Cochrane was one of them.
你就是嫉妒我，因为他是我的好基友，而不是你的了
You’re just jealous ‘cause he’s my best friend now,instead of yours.
听着，你最好留着这个
Look, you better keep this.
怀特・赫斯特，你信不信
Whitehurst,you are without a doubt
最难维持的就是一个军人的仪表
the sorriest excuse for a soldier to ever disgrace these walls.
面对他，你这一辈子都别想消停
Face it, you’re not cut out for this life.
你为什么不帮我个忙
Why don’t you do yourself a favor
滚出肯特军校呢？
and get the hell out of Kent?
如果你能帮我办到，我会的，长官
If I had any choice in the matter,I would, sir.
小滑头
Smart-ass.
滚吧！剪成光头了
Presto! You’re bald.
挺爽
Yeah.
怎么个事？
What the hell?
你是怎么进来的？
How did you get in there?
这个发型明显不合格，大兵
That haircut ain’t regulation, soldier.
你上次剪头是什么时候，嗯？
When’s the last time you had a trim, huh?
和头发吻别吧
Kiss it goodbye.
滚吧！你挂了！
Presto! You’re dead.
没错就是你
It’s definitely you.
我忘了我的....我的...
I just forgot my... My...
嘭！
Boo!
年度军事演习
The annual war games
是肯特军校已经延续了五十年的传统
have been an unbroken tradition here at Kent for over 50 years.
科克伦上尉一直坚信传统的价值
Colonel Cochrane was a man who believed in the value of tradition.
不仅仅是让我们延续下去而已
He not only would have wanted us to go on,
而是命令我们去传承
he’d have ordered us to go on.
因此，军事演习扔按原计划进行
Therefore, the war games will proceed as scheduled.
军校助理谢尔顿上校将带领蓝队
Lieutenant Colonel Shelton will command the blue team.
洛林少校带领红队
Major Rawlings will head up the reds.
任务目标很简单
The objective is simple.
就是夺取对方的队旗
To capture the other team’s flag,
然后安全的带回基地
bring it back here safely to base.
洛林
Rawlings.
出发之前先到军械库领取武器
You will pick up your weapons in the armory before moving out.
你们会使用标准的0-3型爆花弹
You will be using the standard issue Springfield 0-3.
作为弹药
Your ammo.
谢尔顿
Shelton.
如果被打中，就代表阵亡
If you get hit,you are dead.
立刻回基地
Hike back to base.
两位指挥，管好你们的队伍
Cornmanders,take charge of your teams.
最强的队伍必胜
May the best team win.
祝好运，各位
Good luck, men and women.
欢迎入队
Nice of you to join us.
看起来波尼克今天没让你好过
Looks like Botnick’s in a pretty bad mood today.
怎么了？
What’s wrong?
没事，没啥事
Nothing. Nothing’s wrong.
没事，我很好，没事
Nothing’s wrong. I’m fine.Nothing’s wrong.
这个会让疼痛大大减轻的
This ought to slow the pricks down.
一！一！一！
Left! Left! Left!
# 再次踏上征途 #
# Here we go again #
# 带着旧日的枪火 #
# Same old stuff again #
# 行军于大道之上 #
# Marching down the avenue #
# 向前两英里，胜利就在前方 #
# Two more miles, we’ll be through #
# 我会亲自征服你 #
# I’ll be getting rid of you #
# 带着旧日的破枪火 #
# Same old ugly stuff #
# 再次踏上征途 #
# Here we go again #
# 行军于大道之上 #
# Marching down the avenue #
# 向前一英里，胜利就在前方 #
# One more miles, we’ll be through #
# 我会亲自征服你 #
# I’ll be getting rid of you #
怎么了，怀特・赫斯特？
What’s going on,Whitehurst?
你看到了，对不？你看到恰吉了
You saw something,didn’t you? You saw Chucky.
别太懦弱了，怀特・赫斯特
Don’t wimp out on me now, Whitehurst.
我需要你的帮助，那孩子也需要
I need your help.That kid needs your help.
我什么都没看见，行不？
I didn’t see anything, okay?
我压根就什么都没看见
I didn’t see anything at all.
# 你滚吧，对的，你滚吧 #
# You left, right,you left #
# 你的军队滚蛋了 #
# Your military left #
埃尔斯，一定要确定营地周围的安全
Ellis, let’s make sure the perimeters are secured.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
她检查了所有的窗口
She checks all the windows,
然后保姆就听到嘭..嘭..嘭..
and then the babysitter hears this thump, thump.
嘭嘭嘭.
Thumping.
就好像是什么东西在楼上在地板上拖着
Like something’s being dragged across the floor upstairs.
突然她想“我还没有检查孩子”
And suddenly she thinks,‘1 haven’t checked on the children.”
然后她就急忙上楼
So she hurries to the top of the stairs,
然后她到了楼上
and when she gets there,
她看到她的男朋友，被割断了手脚
she sees her boyfriend,completely dismembered,
用下巴一点点的在地板上爬着
dragging himself across the floor by his chin.
嘭...向前滑一下
Thump. Slide.
真恶心
That is gross.
嘿，伙计们，我有个好故事，而且是真的
Hey, you guys,I got a better story and it’s true.
是发生在精神病院的事
It’s about this mental institution,
离这里也没几英里
and it’s a few miles away from here.
嘿
Hey!
希望不是我的故事吓到了你
Hope it wasn’t something I said.
不是，抱歉！
No. I’m sorry.
德・斯尔娃，你认为红队的宿营地会是在哪呢？
De Silva, where do you think the red team’s camped out?
无论在哪
Could be anywhere.
谢尔顿都会找到的，他一直都这样
Shelton’ll find them.He always does.
顺便说下，你可以叫我克里斯汀娜
By the way,you can call me Kristin.
什么？
What?
克里斯汀娜
Kristin.
是我的的名，你的呢？
It’s my first name.Do you have one?
- 安迪 - 啊
- Andy.- Huh
来吧，安迪，给你看点东西
Come on, Andy,I want to show you something.
很酷吧，是吧？
Pretty cool, huh?
是的
Yeah.
我都快忘了还有这种地方
I almost forgot there were places like that.
只让人们感到快乐的地方
People just go to have fun.
听
Listen!
那边有人
Somebody’s out there.
可能是花鼠或者其他的
It’s probably just a chipmunk or something.
没啥能吓到你，是不？
Nothing scares you,does it?
是的
No.
妈的，我真想从这娃娃身体里出去
Man, I really gotta get out of this body.
我要去找泰勒
I’m going after Tyler.
你疯了吗？你找不到他的
Are you crazy? You’ll never find them.
赌点什么？
Wanna bet?
我从谢尔顿营房里偷的
I swiped this from Shelton’s tent.
我们扎营之前，他派出了一个侦察任务
He sent out a reconnaissance mission right before we pitched camp.
红队就在这附近
The red team is somewhere around here.
那孩子有危险，怀特・赫斯特
That kid’s a sitting duck,Whitehurst.
现在，你跟不跟我走？
Now, are you with me or not?
抱歉，不行
I’m sorry, I can’t.
醒醒吧，小姐们，我们出发了
Up and at ‘em, ladies,we’re moving out!
五分钟之内，我要让这个营地成空营
I want this camp to be a ghost town in five minutes!
黎明在出发吧，长官
I thought we weren’t going until dawn, sir.
有人从上尉帐篷里偷走了战术地图
Someone stole the reconnaissance map out of the Colonel’s tent,
因此我们必须要转移
so we’re making our move now.
去准备吧，汉利
Get going, Hanley.
怀特・赫斯特
Whitehurst.
地图被偷了你浑然不觉，是吧？
You wouldn’t know anything about a missing map,would you?
那个混蛋巴克利呢？怀特・赫斯特
Where the hell’s Barclay? Whitehurst!
谢尔顿上校，你最好过来看看
Colonel Shelton,you’d better have a look in here, sir.
怎么了，埃尔斯？
What is it, Ellis?
巴克利擅离职守了，长官
Barclay’s gone AWOL, sir.
他偷走了地图
He stole the map.
这个该死的小叛徒叛变成红队了
That little fucking traitor’s doubling for the reds.
泰勒呢？
Where’s Tyler?
和一个叫查尔斯的擅离职守了
He went AWOL with some guy named Charles.
安迪呢？
Where’s Andy?
怀特・赫斯特，他哪去了？
Whitehurst,where is he?
立，定！
Platoon, halt!
好了，德・斯尔娃你来搜查右翼
All right.De Silva, you’re going to take the right flank.
西格尔，你来搜擦左翼
Siegel, you take the left.I want you to check in
每五分钟电台通报一次
on the radio every five minutes.
- 是的，长官 - 好了，出发吧
- Yes, sir. - All right, move it.
剩下的四处散开
The rest of us are gonna spread out
然后到裂岩谷和埃尔斯会和
and meet up with Ellis at Split Rock.
出发
Move out!
怀特・赫斯特，出发
Whitehurst, move!
谢谢你能来找我
Thanks for coming after me.
不然要朋友干嘛？
What are friends for?
藏起来
Duck.
现在没事了
That was a close one.
我们来玩“灵魂隐匿”吧？
Now, we can play Hide the Soul.
我累了，我不想玩那些无聊游戏了
I’m tired.I don’t want to play that dumb game anymore.
你真是他妈的累赘，知道不？
You’re a fucking drag,you know that?
嘴巴干净点，查尔斯
Watch your mouth,Charles.
别那么和说话
Stop calling me that!
拿刀子干嘛？
What’s the knife for?
一个好士兵是永远在准备战斗的，泰勒
A good soldier is always prepared, Tyler.
巴克利是对的，你不是好家伙
Barclay was right. You’re not a Good Guy.
抱歉，孩子，你对了，我是坏人
Sorry, kid,you got me. I’m bad.
现在，接受现实吧
Now,assume the position.
不要
No!
给我回来
Get back here!
巴克利！巴克利！
Barclay! Barclay!
泰勒
Tyler!
巴克利，你他妈的叛徒，地图还给我
Barclay,you fucking traitor,give me my map!
听我说，谢尔顿
Listen to me, Shelton!
知道我们怎么对待叛徒么,巴克利？
You got any idea what we do to traitors, Barclay?
泰勒有麻烦了
Tyler’s in trouble.
怀特・赫斯特，帮帮我
Come on, Whitehurst,back me up.
埃尔斯少校，召回侧翼人员
Major Ellis,call in the flanks.
是，长官
Yes, sir.
德・斯尔娃，西格尔，是否收到？
De Silva, Siegel,do you copy?
德・斯尔娃，是否收到？
De Silva, do you copy?
德・斯尔娃，请回复
De Silva, come in.
西格尔马上就回来，长官
Siegel’s on his way back, sir.
德・斯尔娃依然没有回复
No word yet from De Silva.
- 继续联系 - 是，长官
- Well, keep trying. - Yes, sir.
救命！救命！
Help! Help!
泰勒
Tyler!
巴克利
Barclay!
你还好吗，泰勒？
Are you okay, Tyler?
看看，看来我们抓到了一个小俘虏
Well, looks like we got ourselves a little POW.
巴克利，你是对的，查尔斯是坏人
Barclay, you were right.Charles is bad.
他刚才要杀我
He tried to hurt me.
查尔斯是他妈谁？
Who the hell’s Charles?
请回复，巴克利，听到请回复！
Come in, Barclay.Come in.
这他妈是谁？
Who the hell is that?
是查尔斯
It’s Charles.
你他妈谁？
Who is this?
让巴克利接，傻瓜
Put Barclay on, jarhead.
是红队的人，他们想玩点花样
It’s the reds.They’re up to something.
你想要什么？
What do you want?
我想要那个小孩
I want the kid.
把他带到破吉普车上，不然你们会付出代价的
Bring him up to the old jeep or there’ll be hell to pay.
- 安迪，别听他的 - 德・斯尔娃
- Andy, don’t do it! - De Silva!
听到没，巴克利？
You hear that,Barclay?
别他妈碰他，你他妈的
Don’t touch her,you son of a bitch.
现在，把那孩子带过来，不然我就宰了她
Now, bring me the kid or I’ll waste her.
红队，红队，回复，红队
Red team, red team.Come in, red team.
我是红队，完毕
This is red team. Over.
破吉普车这边出了点情况
We got a situation up here at the old jeep.
蓝队出现了，建议你们立刻转移
Blue team sighted.Advise you to move your troops in.
希望他们喜欢被牵着鼻子走的感觉
I hope they like the taste of lead.
然后我们就在这坐着，看烟火纷飞
Now just sit back and watch the sparks fly.
好了，你们两个先过去，引他们出来
All right, you two are going to go on up ahead,draw ‘em out.
剩下的把这里包围
The rest of us are gonna circle around.
谢尔顿，这不是游戏
Shelton,this is no game.
我告诉你，这家伙很危险
I’m telling you,this guy is dangerous.
放松，巴克利，都是些颜料
Relax, Barclay.It’s only paint.
好了，出发
All right.Let’s do it.
我好怕，巴克利
I’m scared, Barclay.
是，我也是
Yeah, me, too.
好了，孩子，赶紧过来
All right, kid.Get over here!
不
No.
别他妈涮我
Don’t fuck with me!
我会把你们都炸成片的
I’ll blow all of you to pieces!
滚过去
Beat it.
现在，坐下来，然后闭嘴
Now, just get down and shut up.
好的
Yeah.
啊哦
Ow!
停止射击
Hold your fire!
德・斯尔娃，他们人在哪？
De Silva, where the hell is everybody?
嘿，大兵
Hi, soldier.
卧了个槽
Fuck me.
真够劲
All right!
妈的
Shit!
卧倒
Stay down!
他们用的真子弹
They’re using live rounds!
停止射击！停止射击！
Hold your fire! Hold your fire!
停止射击！
Hold your fire!
哦，天啊，他没有呼吸了，滚开
Oh, God,he’s not breathing.Get away from him!
是你干的，是不？
You did this,didn’t you?
你他妈的狗杂种
You sick son of a bitch!
我要杀了你
Now I’m gonna kill you!
住手，放开他
Stop it! Get off of him!
不是他干的，住手
He didn’t do it! Stop it!
- 再见吧 - 住手
- Let go of me - Stop it!
再见了，混蛋们
Sayonara, suckers.
不！放开她
No! Get off of him!
住手！不是他干的
Stop it! He didn’t do it!
- 再见吧 - 不是他干的，住手
- Let go of me.- He didn’t do it! Stop!
小心
Look out!
不！哦，天啊，怎么回事？
No! Oh, my God,what happened?
是怀特・赫斯特
It’s Whitehurst.
哦，天啊，埃尔斯，埃尔斯，怎么回事？
Oh, my God! Ellis!Ellis, what happened?
爱泼斯坦，到底他妈的怎么回事？
Epstein,what the hell happened?
- 我不知道 - 谁他妈的开的枪？
- I don’t know.- Who fucked with the rifles?
- 我不知道 - 好吧，好吧
- I don’t know - Okay, okay
- 呼叫克拉克 - 是，长官
- Get Clark on the radio.- Yes,sir.
- 马上叫个医生过来 - 是，长官
- And get me a medic up here right now! - Yes, sir.
好了，大家保持镇定
All right. Everybody stay calm!
爱泼斯坦，电台呢，哦，天啊
Epstein, I want that radio! Oh, God.
这是我最后一次警告你
This is the last time I’m gonna tell you.
别管那件事，否则你们都滚出去，你们俩
Give that thing a rest or you’re out of here,both of you.
得了吧，我们没打扰到别人
Come on, we’re not bothering anybody.
你们打扰到我了，消停会
You’re bothering me.Keep it down.
天啊
Jeez!
先生，先生，你得帮帮我
Mister, mister,you’ve got to help me.
怎么了？有什么事？
What’s wrong? What’s the matter?
查尔斯！查尔斯，他在追我
Charles! Charles, he’s after me.
- 谁是查尔斯？- 他是个好家伙玩偶
- Who’s Charles?  - He’s a Good Guy.
- 他想要玩“灵魂隐匿”游戏 - 好，淡定，淡定
- He wants to play Hide the Soul. - Okay, slowdown, slowdown!
坐在这里，你是肯特军校的？
Have a seat over there.Are you from Kent?
- 是，长官 - 你叫啥名，孩子？
- Yes, sir - What’s your name, son?
罗纳德・泰勒，列兵一年级，长官
Ronald Tyler.Private first-class, sir.
坐下，吃点口香糖，列兵？
Have a seat.How about some gum, Private?
我知道当你朋友要对你做坏事，伤害是有多大的
I know how it must hurt when a friend does something bad to you.
确实
Sure does.
但是我想你的朋友...他叫啥来，查尔斯？
But I bet your friend...What’s his name, Charles?
我打赌你的查尔斯并不是故意的
I bet you Charles didn’t mean it.
我打赌他现在一定非常内疚
I bet you he’s really sorry.
不，他没有，他想要杀我
No, he isn’t.He wants to hurt me.
没人要杀你
Nobody’s going to hurt you.
嘿，我知道什么能让你高兴起来
Hey, I know what will cheer you up.
看我发现了什么
Look what I found.
这是你的奖品，拿去吧
Here’s your prize.There you go.
谢谢，老爸
Thank you, Daddy.
我们去坐摩天轮吧
Let’s go in the Super Loop.
好吧
Yeah.
保安办公室&失物招领处
嘿，可能有人看见过它
Hey, maybe somebody’s seen him.
哦，天啊
Oh, God.
- 走吧 - 等等
- Come on - Wait.
妈咪，妈咪，我太喜欢了
Mommy, Mommy,I loved it!
- 你们害怕了吗？ - 没有
- Were you scared? - No!
我们去买点爆米花然后在玩点其他的
Let’s have some popcorn and go on one more ride.
太完美了，进那里去
Perfect. In there.
想都别想
Don’t even think about it.
- 快走 - 好的
- Come on - Okay
警告：闲人禁入
到那里去
In there!
游戏时间到
Time to play.
这看起来不错，停下来
This looks good.Park it.
啊哈
Ah!
哇喔
Whoa!
小子
Kid!
哈！
Ha!
泰勒！
Tyler!
巴克利，巴克利，在这了
Barclay! Barclay! In here!
它手里有枪
He’s got a gun!
小子
Kid!
你还好吧？哦，天啊
Are you okay? Oh, my God.
哦，天啊
Oh, God.
给，拿着
Here. Take it.
你可以的
You can do it.
我会没事的
I’ll be okay.
救命！救命！
Help! Help!
好了，你现在是我的了，泰勒
Yeah! You’re mine now, Tyler!
救命！救命！
Help! Help!
不
No!
泰勒
Tyler!
巴克利
Barclay!
泰勒，小心点
Tyler, watch out!
妈的
Shit!
就这样了，小子！游戏结束
This is it, kid!End of the line.
（喃嘛呢叭咪耍喃嘛呢叭咪耍
我祈求你，赐予我力量吧！
Give me the power,I beg of you!
（喃嘛呢叭咪耍喃嘛呢叭咪耍
加油，双眼睁开，稳住呼吸
Come on,keep both eyes open.Hold your breath.
（喃嘛呢叭咪耍喃嘛呢叭咪耍
耶！
Yeah!
你还好吧？
Are you okay?
嗯
Yeah.
起来，我们得离开这
Come on,let’s get out of here.
抓住，泰勒，抓住
Hold on, Tyler! Hold on!
把他妈孩子给我，他是我的
Give me the fucking kid! He’s mine!
- 救命啊 - 他是我的
- Help! - He’s mine!
把他妈孩子给我
Give me the fucking kid!
抓住，泰勒，抓住
Hold on, Tyler! Hold on!
他是我的
He’s mine!
- 加油，抓住了，泰勒 - 巴克利
- Come on, hold on, Tyler.- Barclay!
给，拿着刀
Here. Take the knife!
把他给我
Give him to me!
拿着，给你，拿着
Take it! Here, take it!
- 巴克利 - 抓住了
- Barclay! - Hold on!
- 接着刀 - 他是我的
- Reach for it! - He ’s mine!
不
No!
泰勒，加油，我抓住你了
Tyler, come on.I got you.
好的，我们马上出发
Okay,we’re on our way in.
收到
Roger.
你现在必须和我们走一趟，孩子
You’ll have to come with us now, son.
你会没事吗？
Are you going to be okay?
别担心，我以前去过那里
Don’t worry.I’ve been here before.
当心脑袋
Watch your head.
谨此，献上李捷妹妹25岁的生日祝福